autosaveenergy.com 2013-07-22

# autosaveenergy.com » Privacy Policy

### About this Notice

We are committed to protecting your privacy and earning your trust every day. This notice describes the personal information we collect about you and how we use and protect it. It applies to our current and former customers and replaces earlier versions that we may have given to you.

### What information do you collect about me?

We consider the information you give us to quote and service your insurance policy to be “Nonpublic Personal Information” if it identifies you and is not available to the public.

### Who do we share your information with?

We will share information about you only as permitted by law. We will not share your Nonpublic Personal Information with other companies.

Disclosures include those that we feel are required to provide insurance claims and customer service, prevent fraud, perform research or comply with the law. Recipients include, our family of insurance companies, their claims representatives, service providers, consumer reporting agencies, law enforcement, courts and government agencies. These parties may disclose the information to others as permitted by law. For example, consumer reporting agencies may disclose transaction information received from us to other insurance companies with which you do business.

Where permitted by law, we may also disclose application or transaction information to service providers that help us market our products.

### Do you protect my information?

We restrict access to your Nonpublic Personal Information to our employees and others who we feel must use it to provide our products and services. Their use of the information is limited by law, our employee code of conduct, and written agreements where appropriate. We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information.

### Why do you collect my email address?

We collect your e-mail address so that we can send you e-mails concerning your transactions with us, and other useful information.

To ensure you get our e-mails, our service provider or we may receive confirmations when you open them or click through the e-mail links. These confirmations may also show whether your e-mail system supports graphics, so we can tailor our messages to you. We will not share your e-mail address with other companies for their marketing purposes.

### Is there additional information for Website visitors?

When you visit our site, we may use information we collect to provide services to you. We use web site information to help understand what you want so that we can enhance your online experience.
